There are how does it get executed actually matters and will impact in fact
它如何执行实际上很重要并且会产生影响
it's not that easy that you what you want become a reality and
你想要的事情变成现实并不那么容易
you have to simulate there are many actors that compete in simulation and
你必须模拟有很多演员在模拟中竞争
Trying to predict which outcome is going to lend you
尝试预测哪种结果会给你带来好处
your swap
你的交换
your intent your LLM calls like the best execution what routes and
你的意图你的法学硕士称之为最好的执行什么路线和
and
和
So this is like essentially like some more
所以这基本上就像更多
Jargons explaining what I was explaining in earlier in the doctor strange analogy
术语解释了我之前在《医生奇怪的类比》中所解释的内容
essentially
本质上
Today you can almost see
今天你几乎可以看到
the block building process for a blockchain as a metaphor
以区块链的区块构建过程作为隐喻
But also have a lot in parallel with a live
而且还有很多并行的直播
reinforcement learning environment
强化学习环境
and
和
Essentially the ground to PNL are the building rewards
PNL 的本质基础是构建奖励
the block rewards for this distributed comment or auction that happens under deadline and
在截止日期内发生的此分布式评论或拍卖的区块奖励，以及
It's a
这是一个
There's a local feedback loop of how do you optimize the execution routes?
有一个关于如何优化执行路线的本地反馈循环？
How do you and there's a global feedback loop of how does the market structure evolve?
您以及市场结构如何演变的全球反馈循环如何？
So in fact, probably the better the more precise term is an evolutionary
所以事实上，可能进化的术语越准确越好
Reinforced learning environment
强化学习环境
Under ever zero condition
在常零条件下
This is actually quite relevant today because if you recall most of your agents most of your LLM's today
这实际上在今天非常相关，因为如果你回忆起你的大多数代理人，你今天的大部分法学硕士
they are trained to
他们受过训练
please you to do what you tell it to do but it's kind of dumb as it they don't have economic rationality as
请你做你告诉它做的事，但这有点愚蠢，因为他们没有经济理性
And they are easily scammed and tricked
他们很容易被欺骗和欺骗
So in fact
所以事实上
One thing that has not been fully explored is that in blockchain
尚未充分探索的一件事是，在区块链中
Especially the block building the simulation process the adversarial simulation
特别是构建模拟过程、对抗性模拟的模块
could actually add
实际上可以添加
value to our
对我们的价值
Progress on the AI front to general intelligence and that is very much
人工智能在通用智能方面取得的进展非常大
Under-appreciated and then a little bit more about this
未被充分重视，然后对此进行更多了解
How
如何
Things work under the hood. How does your intent gets executed and end up landing on chain?
事情在幕后运作。你的意图如何被执行并最终登陆链上？
in the block building process the top of block is the most heated battleground and
在街区建造过程中，街区顶部是最激烈的战场，
Basically who is going for the top of block all of these whether it's cross
基本上谁会去块的顶部所有这些是否是交叉的
Cross venue arbitrage what we call like centralized exchange to decentralized exchange statistical arbitrage or algorithmic liquidations that needs to go
跨场所套利，我们称之为中心化交易所到去中心化交易所的统计套利或需要进行的算法清算
Immediately after an oracle update or oracle driven updates that are just like basically move real-world information on chain
在预言机更新或预言机驱动的更新之后，就像基本上在链上移动真实世界的信息一样
Or market maker quote refresh. Those are essentially high contention
或做市商报价刷新。这些本质上都是高争议的
states
州
that are in competition and
那些处于竞争中的并且
in fact all of them if you squint are
事实上，如果你眯着眼睛看的话，所有这些都是
Oracle updates or the hard work of moving what happens in the real world onto the moodle ledger and
Oracle 更新或将现实世界中发生的事情转移到 Moodle 分类账上的艰苦工作
so
所以
this and so essentially when it comes to
这基本上是当谈到
the block building process and
块构建过程和
How your transaction sorry how your intent gets executed?
您的交易如何让您的意图得到执行？
there is
有
Heated battles in this distributed combinatorial auction across MEV searchers like these arbitrage bots across the
在 MEV 搜索者之间的分布式组合拍卖中，像这些套利机器人一样，展开了激烈的战斗
Solvers for whichever
求解器
Decks that you like to use or aggregators. There's
您喜欢使用的套牌或聚合器。有
aggregators fighting the routing war and
聚合商正在打路由战
There's a block builders that are trying to bid strategically and pack the optimal block
有一个区块建设者正在尝试战略性地竞标并打包最佳区块
This is where how your
这就是你如何
intents
意图
gets translated through market competition into an optimal outcome for
通过市场竞争转化为最优结果
you in
你在
this chaotic process and
这个混乱的过程和
Essentially from the moment you sign a transaction to
本质上从您签署交易的那一刻起
Like a transaction lands on chain
就像交易登陆链上一样
Here is the gap and that gap needs to be held accountable and so and in this chaotic distributed process
这就是差距，这个差距需要承担责任，所以在这个混乱的分布式过程中
Again, there's a natural tendency in these market competition
同样，这些市场竞争有一个自然趋势
to vertically integrate
垂直整合
to centralize because capital begets capital and then
集中化，因为资本产生资本，然后
domain expertise in solving in building or those who have the most water flow or
解决建筑问题的领域专业知识或拥有最多水流或
Will win and continue to win just like
将获胜并继续获胜，就像
Robin Hood and
罗宾汉和
Citadel its relationship
城池与它的关系
Water flow is king and the kingmaker and
水流为王，造王者
Your intent is someone else water flow that they can profit from
您的意图是其他人可以从中获利的水流
So at the end of the day the most important and oftentimes not spoken about
因此，归根结底，最重要且通常没有被提及的
Application design happens really under the hood
应用程序设计真正发生在幕后
To is how do we enable to turn a chaotic
是我们如何能够扭转混乱局面
Competition into a chaotic
竞争陷入混乱
Co-op petition stealing the word of deep hog from Visa
合作社请愿书窃取了 Visa 的 Deep hog 一词
And in fact on aetherium whether it's called proposer builder separation
事实上在以太坊上这是否被称为提议者建设者分离
And
和
Where you see despite?
尽管你在哪里看到的？
as well as where you can see the specialization of
以及您可以在哪里看到专业化
solvers and searchers
求解器和搜索器
that
那
that basically compete on their separate lanes and
基本上在各自的车道上竞争
Then arbitrate it and then the block building process arbitrate
然后仲裁它，然后块构建过程仲裁
in a fair contest who wins and
在公平的竞争中谁获胜
These process
这些过程
Essentially in a permissionless fashion
本质上是一种无需许可的方式
Compose together into a supply chain that
组合成一个供应链
enables the specialized actors to
使专业行动者能够
Do their best work and we call this secure composition
尽力而为，我们称之为安全组合
in distributed block building
在分布式块构建中
So to sum it up like this is a good kind of illustration of what I just said of like you can kind of roughly see
所以总结一下，这是我刚才所说的一个很好的说明，你可以粗略地看到
Like there's an on-chain component from intent submission like to
就像有一个来自意图提交的链上组件一样
finally what goes back on chain, but then what's in the middle is
最后回到链上，但中间的是
all off chain in the attested environments with proofs and
在经过证明的环境中全部脱链，并提供证据和
Like you need to basically rely on and
就像你基本上需要依赖和
Like evidence of what ran a set of other stations a chain of proofs
就像运行一组其他站点的证据一样，一系列的证据
To enable the same guarantees
为了实现相同的保证
Is
是
Executed for your intent
为您的意图而执行
So here I won't go into details
所以这里我就不详细说了
When we speak about attestations
当我们谈论证明时
You can simplify it or the mental model
你可以简化它或心智模型
I like to think about it is essentially break it down into the integrity guarantee confidentiality guarantee and composability guarantee and
我喜欢认为它本质上是将其分解为完整性保证、机密性保证和可组合性保证，
Specifically when I speak about attestation, I think that one of the most important and relevant
具体来说，当我谈到证明时，我认为最重要和最相关的因素之一
Attestation is TE attestation as in block building as in this distributed combinatorial
证明是 TE 证明，就像在这个分布式组合中的块构建一样
Auction under
拍卖下
That's highly
那是高度
adversarial
对抗性的
Essentially TE is the only tool in the near to medium future to ensure
从本质上讲，TE 是在不久的将来确保
Your intent gets executed faithfully
您的意图得到忠实执行
For the optimal quality, but these are
为了获得最佳质量，但这些是
the breakdown of what does the TE attestations used in the block building context can give you and
块构建上下文中使用的 TE 证明可以为您提供哪些详细信息
Finally a bit more about like, you know market microstructure
最后再说一点，你知道市场微观结构
You may wonder why is it the case that every like how do these specialized actors do their best work?
您可能想知道为什么每个人都喜欢这些专业演员如何表现最好？
How does the orchestration happen?
编排是如何发生的？
Ultimately at the end of the day is all about signals
归根结底，信号才是最重要的
Who has what information under this 12-second deadline and
谁在这 12 秒的期限内掌握了哪些信息以及
Who
WHO
whose view like who needs what complementary information and
谁的观点比如谁需要什么补充信息以及
How do you lend compute? How do you share compute in this entire process without?
如何借用计算能力？如果没有的话，您如何在整个过程中共享计算？
Needing to trust your counterparty
需要信任你的交易对手
That's really the end of the day
这真的是一天的结束
How does everything that I'm talking about, you know map on to your
你知道我所说的一切是如何映射到你的身上的
Like the actual market structure and
就像实际的市场结构一样
So like in a nutshell
简而言之
when we think about application design interface fades and
当我们考虑应用程序设计界面消失时
ultimately is the guardrails that
最终是护栏
like
喜欢
Defend the market microstructure that shapes how the market competes and cooperate
捍卫塑造市场竞争与合作方式的市场微观结构
Determines your execution quality and
决定你的执行质量和
I guess my time is almost up. So I'll just speed run it. So how does this tie into
我想我的时间快到了。所以我会加快速度。那么这如何联系到
agentic applications, so the key question we should be asking is when software acts on a human behalf
代理应用程序，因此我们应该问的关键问题是软件何时代表人类行事
like these constraints don't just
就像这些限制不仅仅
prevent like
防止像
abuses by machines and by others
机器和其他人的滥用行为
like these
像这些
What I was speaking about well blockchains and the block building process
我所说的井区块链和区块构建过程
enables and supports and brings to the our real-world application is
启用和支持并将其带入我们的现实世界应用程序是
they can help define the guardrail and constrain what agents are allowed to do and
他们可以帮助定义护栏并限制允许代理执行的操作
So
所以
essentially like when you look at how far we've gotten since the inception of DeFi in 2018 19
本质上就像你看看自 2018 年 DeFi 诞生以来我们已经走了多远 19
To essentially 296 agentic application in agentic execution. I would say one of the key Delta is this
296 代理执行中的代理应用程序。我想说关键的三角洲之一就是这个
accountability for the invisible routing proprietary execution and outcome attribute
对隐形路由专有执行和结果属性的责任
attribution
归因
Like receipts for outcome attribution that become available
就像可用的结果归因收据一样
in other words
换句话说
What is in the red now? We can help them accountable through verifiable off-chain
现在红色是什么？我们可以通过可验证的链下帮助他们承担责任
Infrastructure that works in conjunction with on-chain
与链上协同工作的基础设施
smart contracts and
智能合约和
So like and all of what I was saying earlier when I speak about trading bots when I speak about MEV boss
就像我之前谈到交易机器人、谈到 MEV 老板时所说的那样
Solvers aggregators. These are all just spots and you can think about them in a meta level
求解器聚合器。这些都只是点，你可以在元层面上思考它们
in parallel with agents and
与代理人并行
Except that agents they work in a non-atomic way and it's a multi-step
除了代理以非原子方式工作并且这是一个多步骤
process and
过程和
but the same microstructure that we spoke about earlier where
但我们之前谈到的相同微观结构
Power is concentrated and agency is taken away from your hands. It still applies in
权力集中，代理权从你手中被夺走。它仍然适用于
this
这
agentic
代理的
application design paradigm
应用程序设计范式
the only Delta that you need to be more mindful of is delegation or is
您唯一需要更加注意的 Delta 是授权，或者是
Do you trust your agent to take over your accounts on social media?
您信任您的代理人接管您在社交媒体上的帐户吗？
Take care of your email accounts take over your
照顾好您的电子邮件帐户，接管您的
entire
全部的
operating systems
操作系统
That you rely upon
你所依赖的
At what point can you trust them? In fact, if you think about it, this is the same question that you should ask yourself when they think about
什么时候你可以信任他们？事实上，如果你仔细想想，当他们思考时，你应该问自己同样的问题
approvals
批准
signing transactions on block chains and
在区块链上签署交易以及
in fact
实际上
despite all of the recent hacks I
尽管最近发生了所有的黑客攻击，我
would say that
会说
On-chain applications or smart contract applications in aetherium, especially the work around account abstraction has
以太坊中的链上应用程序或智能合约应用程序，特别是围绕帐户抽象的工作已经
significantly
显著地
Advanced and leaf rocked. I think the state-of-the-art in terms of secure account delegation in
先进和叶子摇晃。我认为在安全帐户委托方面最先进的
the web to world
网络到世界
as well as in agentic
以及代理方面
applications
应用
in other words in
换句话说
agent to agent communications off
座席间通讯已关闭
Authorization it's not soft
授权并不软
but blockchain has close to
但区块链已经接近
What we have what we see what I see as a solution much closer
我们所拥有的，我们所看到的，我所看到的更接近的解决方案
Big and it's been battle-tested under adversarial conditions with real money
规模很大，并且已经在对抗条件下用真钱进行了战斗测试
at the table, so
在餐桌上，所以
Now the key question, you know to sum everything all up what to build. How do we?
现在的关键问题是，您知道将所有内容总结起来要构建什么。我们怎么办？
Enable human centric agency and in light and extend it to agent mediated future. That's the question and
实现以人为中心的代理，并将其扩展到以代理为中介的未来。这就是问题和
Here are some more technical jargons
这里有一些更多的技术术语
But in the nutshell a lot of these design considerations are
但简而言之，这些设计考虑因素中有很多是
What we've been designing for in smart contract applications on the blockchain substrate the same design pattern design philosophy
我们在区块链底层上的智能合约应用程序中设计的目的是相同的设计模式设计理念
that should be applied to agentic application applications and
应该应用于代理应用程序和
A simple task
一个简单的任务
like this
像这样
actually
实际上
entails like every single decision that we just discussed the complexity that's hidden away from you under the hood
就像我们刚才讨论的每一个决定一样，隐藏在幕后的复杂性
To be trustworthy
值得信赖
To be accountable and that requires founded authority
承担责任，这需要有权威的基础
verifiable execution
可验证的执行
neutral coordination and
中立协调和
Give us the right to refuse or in other words a better UX for approval
给我们拒绝的权利，或者换句话说，给我们更好的用户体验以供批准
or in other words a better UX and period and
或者换句话说，更好的用户体验和周期
So yeah in a nutshell
是的，简而言之
The key to
关键是
application design with agency is
与代理的应用程序设计是
execution
执行
That's accountable and this is the distributed coordination problem that blockchains
这是负责任的，这就是区块链的分布式协调问题
When smart contracts have been solving and we're solving them at scale
当智能合约已经解决并且我们正在大规模解决它们时
Yeah, so here's a
是的，所以这是一个
simplification
简化
Blockchains would like to show layers. So this is one way you can
区块链希望显示层次。所以这是你可以的一种方法
Think about it. There goes your base layer that unerise and finalizes
想一想。你的基础层消失并最终确定
your shared reality
你们共同的现实
But then the starting point is always your human intent. What do you actually want?
但出发点始终是你的人类意图。你到底想要什么？
and then the rest that's
然后剩下的就是
Bracketed a lot of our work at flashbots is here on execution markets
我们在 flashbots 的很多工作都集中在执行市场上
resolving
解决
competing intense
竞争激烈
resolving contention of states and
解决国家之间的争端
Through this distributed combinatorial auction
通过这种分布式组合拍卖
To pack the optimal block select one canonical outcome that is best in your interest
要打包最佳块，请选择最符合您利益的规范结果
So remember dr. Strange, I just want you to leave with that image
所以请记住博士。奇怪，我只是想让你带着那张照片离开
Millions of futures gets enumerated and simulated one gets selected. Do you want that one outcome?
数以百万计的期货被枚举并模拟，其中一个被选择。你想要这样的结果吗？
To be that to be what's in your favor if that's the case
如果是这样的话，那就成为对你有利的事情
Care about what happens under the hood
关心幕后发生的事情
All right, that's it. Thank you
好吧，就是这样。谢谢
Thank you, Tina
谢谢你，蒂娜
Thank You Tina
谢谢蒂娜
While we get the stage set up for our next session a quick note for those who may just have joined us
当我们为下一次会议做好准备时，请为那些可能刚刚加入我们的人提供一个简短的说明
Today's gathering is hosted by the aetherium application guild aka EAG a global nonprofit
今天的聚会由以太坊应用程序协会（又名 EAG）主办，这是一家全球非营利组织
collaborative organization
协作组织
Dedicated to advancing the innovation adoption and the real-world impact of aetherium native applications
致力于推动以太坊本机应用程序的创新采用和现实世界影响
Up next we will move on to an exciting panel discussion titled institutional adoption on aetherium
接下来我们将进行一场激动人心的小组讨论，题为“以太坊的机构采用”
challenges gaps and the path forward
挑战差距和前进道路
Let's welcome the moderator QZ partner of aetherium ecosystem fund
欢迎以太坊生态基金主持人QZ合伙人
The panelists are Patrick McCoury
小组成员是帕特里克·麦考里
researcher at Arbitrum Foundation
Arbitrum 基金会研究员
Mojalin
莫贾林
institutional privacy lead at is aetherium foundation
以太坊基金会机构隐私主管
Serena Wong head of
黄瑟琳娜的头
HSK Ecolabs at Hushkey group and Samuel Chong
Hushkey 集团和 Samuel Chong 的 HSK Ecolabs
institutional relations lead APAC and Mina at LIDL ecosystem foundation
LIDL 生态系统基金会亚太地区机构关系主管和 Mina
Please welcome them up. Hi everyone
请欢迎他们上来。大家好
So today's panel is about institutional adoption. So we've got a very illustrious group across the entire industry
所以今天的小组讨论是关于机构采用的。所以我们拥有整个行业非常杰出的团队
I'm gonna just jump right into it because I think we might be a bit short of time
我要直接开始，因为我想我们的时间可能有点短
so
所以
Today actually I want to frame the session with our provocation, which is that?
今天实际上我想用我们的挑衅来安排会议，那是什么？
Institutional adoption is usually represented as validation
机构采用通常表现为验证
but
但
I'm curious right like what if institutions are adopting aetherium for something quite different from what we have actually built
我很好奇，如果机构采用以太坊来实现与我们实际构建的东西完全不同的东西会怎样？
And so that will be the core tension of today's discussion
这将是今天讨论的核心张力
and I'm gonna start with Patrick from Arbitrum and
我将从 Arbitrum 的 Patrick 开始
For you you've been particularly vocal about pushing institutions towards self-custody and using more multi-six
对于您来说，您特别热衷于推动机构实行自我托管并使用更多的多六
safe hardware wallets
安全的硬件钱包
the whole stack
整个堆栈
But for a finance person signing a million dollar transaction and being asked to verify call data
但对于财务人员签署一百万美元的交易并被要求验证通话数据
Intendedly that that's genuinely terrifying
故意说这真的很可怕
The UX doesn't match the ask what do you have to say about this?
用户体验与问题不符，您对此有何评论？
Yeah, I mean let me set the scene first before I get into the you know
是的，我的意思是让我先设置场景，然后再进入你知道的
My rant about the UX of crypto right now. So as most people here are aware
我现在对加密货币的用户体验的咆哮。所以正如这里的大多数人都知道的那样
Ethereum has existed for about ten years and defies about seven years old and
以太坊已经存在了大约十年，并且已经存在了大约七年了
For about the past seven years. We've built these really cool defy primitives that are just minimized and obviously they're smart contracts and they're autonomous
过去七年左右。我们已经构建了这些非常酷的 defy 原语，它们只是最小化，显然它们是智能合约并且是自治的
But with these defy protocols they've been built using food coins and meme coins and not real assets
但这些违抗协议是使用食物币和模因币而不是真实资产构建的
But in 2025 2026 and onwards we're now starting to see this intersection between
但从 2025 年、2026 年起，我们现在开始看到两者之间的交叉点
DeFi and obviously trotify and real-world assets
DeFi 以及明显的 trotify 和现实世界资产
So now we're going to see RWAs land on aetherium and interact with these defy
所以现在我们将看到 RWA 登陆以太坊并与这些挑战互动
Primitives that we've built for the past seven years and that's really really exciting and like I don't know like it gets me really
我们在过去七年里构建的基元，这真的非常令人兴奋，我不知道它是否真的让我着迷
Like, you know bubbly when I when I hear about it
就像，当我听到这件事时你就知道了
But the problem is that for the past seven years the prime user of defy has been technical folk or developers
但问题是，在过去的七年里，defy 的主要用户一直是技术人员或开发人员
Or people who understand how the system works
或者了解系统如何运作的人
So let me ask people in the audience here if I can grab your attention
所以让我问问这里的观众是否可以引起你们的注意
I just have like one or two questions to get a sense of your experience
我只是想了解一两个问题来了解一下您的经历
So raise your hand if you have ever used a hardware wallet
如果您曾经使用过硬件钱包，请举手
Who's ever tried using a hardware wallet before?
谁曾经尝试过使用硬件钱包？
Cool a few people over there. I see a few people we see some OGs
冷静一下那边的几个人。我看到了一些人，我们看到了一些 OG
Okay, cool. And then raise your hand if you enjoyed using a hardware wallet
好吧，酷。如果您喜欢使用硬件钱包，请举手
No one's ever knowns reason their hand on down there. Look at that. That's the true dev got a core dev down there
没有人知道他们把手放在那里的原因。看看那个。这才是真正的开发者，那里有一个核心开发者
And that's my point like hardware wallets are
这就是我的观点，就像硬件钱包一样
Really difficult to use they're terrifying you look at the screen and it just has this hash of a blind signing mode
真的很难使用，它们让你看着屏幕感到害怕，它只有盲签名模式的哈希值
So you have no idea what you're even signing and then once you sign it
所以你根本不知道你要签署什么，一旦你签署了
You're about to transfer millions of dollars if you're like an institution and then you visit the website for these monthly sakes
如果您像一个机构一样，然后您出于每月的目的访问该网站，那么您将要转移数百万美元
I mean we do use gnosis safe by complain about it all the time
我的意思是我们确实通过一直抱怨来使用 gnosis safe
You go on this website and it's somewhat terrifying for financial like anyone who's not a dev
你访问这个网站，就像任何非开发人员一样，这对于财务人员来说有点可怕
They look at it. They simulate the transaction. They go in tenderly they see code
他们看着它。他们模拟交易。他们温柔地走进去，看到代码
They see hashes and they're just like all I want to do is you know deposit into a defy protocol
他们看到哈希值，就像我想做的就是将钱存入 Defy 协议
I have no idea what's going on here
我不知道这里发生了什么
And so the issue we have as an industry is that the defy primitives are there they work
因此，作为一个行业，我们面临的问题是，defy 原语是否有效
They're bottle tested for seven years
它们经过了七年的瓶子测试
But the UX has not caught up because we've not really had real-world assets and real, you know finance users
但用户体验还没有跟上，因为我们还没有真正拥有现实世界的资产和真正的金融用户
Tradfied users interacting with the chain and that's really the next thing we need to fix
Tradfied 用户与链交互，这确实是我们接下来需要解决的问题
UI is like the next frontier for the next couple of years and
UI 就像未来几年的下一个前沿
Yeah, that's my rant over basically I can I could go on but even screenshots and everything
是的，这就是我的咆哮，基本上我可以我可以继续，但甚至截图和一切
But I think most people get the point
但我想大多数人都明白这一点
We really need to work on the UX because it's terrifying for tradfied people and they're going to be the real users over the next
我们确实需要在用户体验方面下功夫，因为这对于被交易的人来说是可怕的，而他们将在接下来的时间里成为真正的用户
four years
四年
Absolutely, I definitely agree with that that when I sign my hardware wallet, I get a heart attack
绝对，我绝对同意，当我签署我的硬件钱包时，我会心脏病发作
Shut a vodka
闭上一杯伏特加
You gotta be very brave
你必须非常勇敢
So that's one point that I think institutions need to do a bit better about which is UX, right?
所以我认为机构需要在用户体验方面做得更好一点，对吗？
So the other point I think is actually about education
所以我认为另一点实际上是关于教育
And so this question is actually for Mo who works for the Ethereum Foundation's
所以这个问题实际上是针对以太坊基金会工作的 Mo 提出的。
institutional privacy lead now
机构隐私现在处于领先地位
One thing that we have discovered over the years is that the strongest institutional relationships with Ethereum have not come from like
多年来我们发现的一件事是，与以太坊最牢固的机构关系并不是来自像
Directly trying to pitch them. Can you use the theorem? Can you use Eve like that? It's not very effective
直接尝试向他们推销。你能用定理吗？你能这样利用伊芙吗？这不是很有效
so we are curious that
所以我们很好奇
for
为了
Ethereum what is
以太坊是什么
Ethereum is very challenging to navigate without a guide and I think for you
在没有指南的情况下，以太坊是非常具有挑战性的，我认为对你来说
That's something that you have been playing a role for different institutions from a very personal matter
这是你一直在为不同机构发挥的非常个人的作用
And so I'm curious that when as part of the privacy task force where institutions engage
所以我很好奇，当机构参与隐私工作组时
Directly with a specific problem and found their way into Ethereum
直接解决特定问题并进入以太坊
What is the right model in your opinion for engaging institutions?
您认为吸引机构参与的正确模式是什么？
Yeah, so I definitely think that first of the word institutions is very broad. There are many different types
是的，所以我绝对认为第一个词机构非常广泛。有很多不同的类型
But the way that you engage them is predominantly I think
但我认为你与他们互动的方式主要是
The same or the way it should be done which is
相同或应该这样做的方式是
Understanding what they're trying to do for a lot of these folks. They don't necessarily understand
了解他们正在努力为这些人做些什么。他们不一定明白
Blockchains that well, they don't necessarily understand their forness as they give them
区块链那么好，他们不一定了解它们所提供的特性
But what they do know is maybe the problems that they're working on. I think what's the great thing about
但他们所知道的也许是他们正在解决的问题。我想有什么了不起的
An ecosystem like a theorem is that you know, you can help them solve moving money. You can help them solve identity
一个生态系统就像一个定理，你知道，你可以帮助他们解决转移资金的问题。你可以帮助他们解决身份问题
But what they get without almost not knowing is that they also get this like really large open infrastructure
但他们几乎不知道的是，他们也得到了像真正大型开放基础设施一样的东西
One that's like battle-tested and resilient
一款经过战斗考验且有弹性的产品
one that can't censor them and
一个无法审查它们的人
I think like the model there is as you suggested like understanding what they're doing, but then there is this gap
我认为就像你建议的模型一样，了解他们在做什么，但是存在差距
Where they don't quite understand the additional properties that they get that is extremely beneficial to them and they realize that over time. So I think
他们不太了解他们获得的额外属性对他们极其有益，并且随着时间的推移他们意识到这一点。所以我认为
Yes, that's definitely the model and then the scaling aspect of that
是的，这绝对是模型，然后是它的缩放方面
I think is an interesting one, which is like goes back to education
我认为这是一个有趣的事情，就像回到了教育
Heading to understand why these things are important why we care about these properties why we've been working in this space for 10 years
想要了解为什么这些事情很重要为什么我们关心这些属性为什么我们在这个领域工作了 10 年
and
和
That's where we need to rely on the ecosystem
这就是我们需要依赖生态系统的地方
So, you know, I work at the foundation but really for this to be successful
所以，你知道，我在基金会工作，但真正的目的是为了取得成功
It has to be an ecosystem effort has to be from folks that work at Arbitrum folks that work in you know
它必须是一个生态系统的努力，必须来自在 Arbitrum 工作的人们，你知道的
There's different organization all across the world
世界各地都有不同的组织
And I think if we do that and we create like open specs and general knowledge that people can leverage
我认为如果我们这样做，我们就会创建人们可以利用的开放规范和常识
That is the best way forward. It's still that education gap and having a place where people can refer to that
这是最好的前进方向。仍然是教育差距，并且有一个地方可以供人们参考
So folks like Arbitrum, Hashkey
所以像 Arbitrum、Hashkey 这样的人
All doing great work and please continue doing so definitely just a quick follow-up question
所有人都做得很好，请继续这样做，这绝对只是一个快速的后续问题
I think one feedback that we've gotten in the space is that Ethereum tends to
我认为我们在该领域得到的一个反馈是以太坊倾向于
invent a lot of new words
发明了很多新词
What are some
有哪些
Better suggestions you have to better translate and make what we do legible to institutions
您必须更好地翻译更好的建议，并使我们所做的事情对机构来说易于理解
I think this is where it's really important to have people that have some domain expertise in what that institution is doing
我认为这就是拥有对该机构正在做的事情具有一定领域专业知识的人员的真正重要之处
So it could be for example
所以它可以是例如
Educational space it could be bio
教育空间可能是生物空间
It could be pharma it could be finance and then once you understand what they're looking for you're able to translate
可能是制药，也可能是金融，一旦您了解他们在寻找什么，您就可以翻译
There are various different affordances. So a lot of people often talk about censorship resistance
有各种不同的可供性。所以很多人经常谈论审查制度抵抗
And for you know many organizations what that means that there's less
对于许多组织来说，这意味着更少
counterparty risk being able to understand that their language and translate that I think is the way forward and in order to do that
交易对手有可能理解他们的语言并进行翻译，我认为这是前进的方向，为了做到这一点
It's I think almost the most Ethereum way is to be collaborative
我认为大多数以太坊方式就是协作
Work with others understand where they're coming from and then use that as a bridge to help communicate what we can give them
与他人合作，了解他们的来源，然后以此为桥梁，帮助沟通我们可以为他们提供什么
So since we are still on the topic of institutions, let me have the next question for hash key
既然我们仍然在讨论机构的话题，那么让我问下一个关于哈希键的问题
So
所以
Serena
瑟琳娜
First time seeing you hash key has been a great supporter of Ethereum for quite a few years already
第一次看到你的哈希密钥已经是以太坊好几年的大力支持者了
Yeah, and I'm curious because hash key both
是的，我很好奇，因为哈希键都是
Serves institutions and it's kind of become a large enough organization that some of us would consider them an institution
为机构服务，它已经成为一个足够大的组织，我们中的一些人会认为它们是一个机构
Yeah, so I'm curious when you talk to different organizations about Ethereum
是的，所以我很好奇当你与不同的组织谈论以太坊时
What is the first objection that you usually hear and how do you help to alleviate it to help them to understand?
您通常听到的第一个反对意见是什么？您如何帮助减轻这种反对意见以帮助他们理解？
What are some of these affordances that Ethereum might bring to them?
以太坊可能会给他们带来哪些可供性？
Okay, it's great to be here. Yeah. Well, hash key is in our unique position
好的，很高兴来到这里。是的。嗯，哈希键处于我们独特的位置
Yeah, first of all, we are a licensed and the regulated group
是的，首先，我们是有执照且受监管的团体
Yeah, so we speak the language of compliance
是的，所以我们讲的是合规语言
But we also build our own hash key chain. Yeah, yeah, it's serum. Yeah
但我们也构建了自己的哈希密钥链。是的，是的，这是血清。是的
when the
当
Institute institutions sit down with us as a conversation is
研究所机构与我们坐下来进行对话
Narrowby like is a serum is central
狭窄的就像是血清是中心
Decentralized enough. Yeah, so real talk will be like that side if something goes wrong on chain who is accountable?
足够去中心化。是的，所以真正的谈话会是这样的，如果链上出现问题谁负责？
Yeah, they wanted to know the
是的，他们想知道
clearly
清楚地
Clearly chair of restability. Yeah, so they could
显然椅子的稳定性。是的，所以他们可以
have the proper explanation to their legal counsel well like
向他们的法律顾问做出适当的解释，就像
Compliance officer and so on. Yeah
合规官等。是的
So that's why
所以这就是为什么
Our hash key chain. Mmm. Yeah lead leads to you. So we wanted to meet the gap between the complaints
我们的哈希钥匙链。嗯。是的，铅通向你。所以我们想要弥补投诉之间的差距
and the institutions to the crypto. So
以及加密货币的机构。所以
Yeah, mmm
是啊，嗯
Yeah, and we wanted to put you know, the plans as a first feature into the
是的，我们想让你知道，这些计划是第一个功能
infra, yeah
下图，是的
So it's quite brave for hash key to be taking that approach
所以哈希键采取这种方法是相当勇敢的
Especially when you talk about being compliant as a as a regulated entity. Yeah
尤其是当您谈论作为受监管实体的合规性时。是的
Yeah, just think so. I think that's a very unique perspective
是的，只是这么想。我认为这是一个非常独特的视角
for all of us
对于我们所有人
And honestly, it's it's really incredible that hash key has taken the step forward to move beyond just like very typical
老实说，哈希键已经向前迈出了一步，超越了非常典型的情况，这真是令人难以置信
Kind of like trading activities and this kind of thing. So
有点像贸易活动之类的事情。所以
my question for you, I suppose is
我想问你的问题是
What why have you or why do you think hash key has taken a step forward and chosen Ethereum?
您为什么或者您认为哈希密钥向前迈出了一步并选择了以太坊？
Yeah, I think
是的，我想
Maybe the complaints want us to do that
也许投诉希望我们这样做
yeah, because you know, we are based in Hong Kong and you know a lot of
是的，因为你知道，我们的总部设在香港，你知道很多
Institutionals from tried to fire around of us and when
机构试图在我们周围开火，当
They'd wanna you know
他们想让你知道
Get the eyesight to the market what they mainly care about is you know
洞察市场 他们最关心的是你知道
Is that safe or security do you have KYC? Yeah, do you have the transfer restrictions? How do you?
您有 KYC 吗？安全吗？对了，有转账限制吗？你怎么样？
Meet the you know requirements for the government or for example AML. Yeah, so I think
满足您所知的政府要求或例如反洗钱要求。是的，所以我想
is
是
It's a new trend of industry. Yeah to be a compliance chain. Yeah
这是行业的新趋势。是的，成为一个合规链。是的
Maybe I can add a bit more to that people don't mind. I think another thing that we've found is that
也许我可以补充一点人们不介意的内容。我认为我们发现的另一件事是
basically Ethereum has been
基本上以太坊已经